Guide to the Records of Graham Windham 1804-2011 MS 2916
New-York Historical Society
- Series III - Graham Windham, 1970-2011 (bulk 1977-2010)
  - Subseries III.7 - Office of Development - Administrative Materials, 1983-2011 (bulk 1990-1996)
    - Board Member John Sargent, 1992 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 20)
    - Board Member Andrew Saunders, 1992 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 21)
    - Board Member Harriet H. Savage, 1992 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 22)
    - Board Member Bruce Schnitzer, 1992 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 23)
    - Board Member David Shatz, 1992 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 24)
    - Board Member Miles Slater, 1992 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 25)
    - Board Member Richard Stewart, Jr., 1992 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 26)
    - Board Member Marian Taylor, 1992 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 27)
    - Board Member Catherine Tracy, 1992 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 28)
    - Board Member Sandra Trim-Dacosta, 1991 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 29)
    - Board Member H.M. Baird Voorhis, 1992 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 30)
    - Board Member Georgia Wall, 1992 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 31)
    - Bio of Celeste Weisglass, undated (Offsite-box 76, Folder 32)
    - Bio of Stephen Weisglass, undated (Offsite-box 76, Folder 33)
    - Board Member Phyllis Wright, 1992 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 34)
    - Joyce Lapenn Bio, 1991 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 35)
    - Joyce Lapenn Who's Who Application, 1990 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 36)
    - Speeches by Suzie Bales and Joyce Lapenn, 1991 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 37)
    - Poul Jensen Bio, undated (Offsite-box 76, Folder 38)
    - Staff bios: L. Stafford, C. Boakye, P. Dunn, R. Primason, Fatima Goldman, 1992 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 39)
    - The Reverend Tony Hart, Staff Member, 1974 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 40)
    - Interview Questions for Alumni at Reunion, 2004 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 41)
    - Gilbert Harris, Resident in 1957, 2004 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 42)
    - Frank Michaels, former resident at campus, 2004 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 43)
    - Case Vignettes - RESTRICTED, 1989 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 44)
    - Success Stories from Field - Children - RESTRICTED, 1989 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 45)
    - Communications Improvement Committee Minutes, 1991 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 46)
    - Budget, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 47)
    - Group Homes Incidents - RESTRICTED, 1992 (Offsite-box 76, Folder 48)
    - Budget, 1993 (Offsite-box 77, Folder 1)
    - Poul Jensen's Memo to Board on Past Year, 1999 (Offsite-box 77, Folder 2)
    - Budget and Goals, 2000 (Offsite-box 77, Folder 3)
    - Computer Project - Early Childhood, 1995 (Offsite-box 77, Folder 4)
    - Quality Assurance Reports, 1996 (Offsite-box 77, Folder 5)
    - Literacy Program Grants including Morgan Stanley Financial Report, 1999 (Offsite-box 77, Folder 6)
    - Power Point Presentation, 2005 (Offsite-box 77, Folder 7)
    - Letters re: Ancestors - RESTRICTED, 2005 (Offsite-box 77, Folder 8)
    - Adoptive Parent Bios - RESTRICTED, undated (Offsite-box 77, Folder 9)
    - Consent Forms, 1987 (Offsite-box 77, Folder 10)
    - Release Form - Every Child Brochure, 1988 (Offsite-box 77, Folder 11)
    - Finest Care Photo Releases, 1990 (Offsite-box 77, Folder 12)
    - Campus Talent Releases in a PSA, 1992 (Offsite-box 77, Folder 13)
    - NFSC Photo Release, 1993 (Offsite-box 77, Folder 14)
    - Consent for Photographs, 1994 (Offsite-box 77, Folder 15)
    - Harlem Child Care Center Releases, 1995 (Offsite-box 77, Folder 16)
    - Williamsburg Day Care Release, 1995 (Offsite-box 77, Folder 17)
    - Beacon Center Media Consent, 1996 (Offsite-box 77, Folder 18)
    - Grow With Us Consent Form, 1996 (Offsite-box 77, Folder 19)
    - Project Welcome Home Release Form, 1996 (Offsite-box 77, Folder 20)
  - Subseries III.8 - Office of Development - Press Releases, Articles and Clippings, 1975-2010
    Subseries III.8 is the third of four subseries of materials from the Graham Windham Office of Development. The subseries contains nine boxes and three binders of press releases, articles, and clippings produced and/or collected by the Office of Development. Materials are arranged sometimes by subject and sometimes by date. In general, with a few exceptions, press releases are at the beginning of the subseries, followed by clippings and articles. The three binders of clippings are arranged at the end of the subseries, and include clippings that pre-date the merger of Graham and Windham. All other materials are from 1977-2010, with the majority of materials from the 1990's. Materials from earlier dates are sometimes arranged after later dates. Original folder titles have been maintained.
    - Press Releases re: Campus, 1977-1984 (Offsite-box 78, Folder 1)
    - Press Releases Miscellaneous Various Programs, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 78, Folder 2)
    - Press Releases Miscellaneous Various Programs and Campus Board, 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 78, Folder 3)
    - Press Releases Miscellaneous, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 78, Folder 4)
    - Press Releases Miscellaneous Programs incl. health fairs, board, staff and campus, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 78, Folder 5)
    - Press Release Harlem Child Care Opening, 1993 (Offsite-box 78, Folder 6)
    - Press Release - Family Matters, 1994 August (Offsite-box 78, Folder 7)
    - Press Release - Family Matters, 1994 October (Offsite-box 78, Folder 8)
    - Press Release - Family Matters, 1994 November-December (Offsite-box 78, Folder 9)
    - Harlem Week Barbecue, 1994 August (Offsite-box 78, Folder 10)
    - Halloween on Ice Benefit, 1994 October (Offsite-box 78, Folder 11)
    - Rwanda Project, GW's Gift to Unicef, 1994 October (Offsite-box 78, Folder 12)
    - Rwanda Relief Articles, 1994 (Offsite-box 78, Folder 13)
    - Rwanda Charity Car Wash, 1994 September (Offsite-box 78, Folder 14)
    - Williamsburg Child Care Center Welcomes 2 Year Olds, 1994 October (Offsite-box 78, Folder 15)
    - Holiday Happenings for Children, 1994 December (Offsite-box 78, Folder 16)
    - Kermit the Frog Hops in to Help Santa, 1994 December (Offsite-box 78, Folder 17)
    - Holiday Story, Santa Visits Kids, 1994 December (Offsite-box 78, Folder 18)
    - Bronxville Volunteers Receive Community Service Citation, named for Eleanor Roosevelt, 1994 December (Offsite-box 78, Folder 19)
    - 189th Annual Meeting, 1995 May (Offsite-box 78, Folder 20)
    - Beacon Center Takes Part in New York Cares Day, 1995 October (Offsite-box 78, Folder 21)
    - Press release re: Proposed Budget Cuts to Child Care Services, 1995 May (Offsite-box 78, Folder 22)
    - Citibank Tennis Benefit, 1995 August and September (Offsite-box 78, Folder 23)
    - ESH [Elizabeth Schuyler Hamilton] Scholars - Press Releases, 1995 (Offsite-box 78, Folder 24)
    - Donna Hanover Giuliani and Charlayne Hunter-Gault Honored at 9th Annual Gala, 1995 April and May (Offsite-box 78, Folder 25)
    - Family Matters, Public Service Column, 1995 February (Offsite-box 78, Folder 26)
    - Press Releases, 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 79, Folder 1)
    - Press Releases, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 79, Folder 2)
    - Press Releases, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 79, Folder 3)
    - GW Programs and Other Agency Programs, 1990-1995 (Offsite-box 79, Folder 4)
    - Troubled Kids, Troubled Homes? Education etc., 1994 (Offsite-box 79, Folder 5)
    - Health and Children, 1994-1995 (Offsite-box 79, Folder 6)
    - Health and Children, 1994-1995 (Offsite-box 79, Folder 7)
    - Child Care, All Work No Pay, 1995 (Offsite-box 79, Folder 8)
    - GW Family Matters Program re: After School Learning, 1995 (Offsite-box 79, Folder 9)
    - Tennis Legends Compete in Rye/Graham Windham Beneficiary, 1995 (Offsite-box 79, Folder 10)
    - Profile of Sofiya Rusakova, Social Worker at GW, 1995 (Offsite-box 79, Folder 11)
    - Bronxville High School Seniors Give Back to Community at Campus, 1996 (Offsite-box 79, Folder 12)
    - Project Welcome Home, 1997 (Offsite-box 79, Folder 13)
    - Family Matters Public Service Column, 1995 March (Offsite-box 80, Folder 1)
    - Family Matters Monthly Column, 1995 April (Offsite-box 80, Folder 2)
    - Family Matters Monthly Column, 1995 May (Offsite-box 80, Folder 3)
    - Family Matters: School's Over, but Learning's Not Yet, 1995 July (Offsite-box 80, Folder 4)
    - Family Matters Monthly Column, 1995 August (Offsite-box 80, Folder 5)
    - Family Matters Monthly Column, 1995 September (Offsite-box 80, Folder 6)
    - Family Matters Monthly Column, 1995 November (Offsite-box 80, Folder 7)
    - Greenburgh-Graham School Graduation, 1995 June (Offsite-box 80, Folder 8)
    - Harlem Child Care Center Celebrates Black History Month, 1995 March (Offsite-box 80, Folder 9)
    - Harlem Child Care Center First Graduation, 1995 June (Offsite-box 80, Folder 10)
    - Hastings Fire Department 25th Annual Christmas Visit to Campus, 1995 January (Offsite-box 80, Folder 11)
    - Senior Artisans Bring Handmade gifts to Formerly Homeless Mothers and Their Babies, 1995 June (Offsite-box 80, Folder 12)
    - Team Career Conference, 1995 March (Offsite-box 80, Folder 13)
    - Three Kings Day Celebration at Family Day Care, 1995 January (Offsite-box 80, Folder 14)
    - Event Advisory re: Olympic Torch, 1995 October (Offsite-box 80, Folder 15)
    - Preventive Services Directors Applauded by Community Leaders in Brooklyn, 1995 October (Offsite-box 80, Folder 16)
    - Beacon Center Aerobics Classes, 1996 August (Offsite-box 80, Folder 17)
    - Beacon Center First Day of Summer Camp, 1996 July (Offsite-box 80, Folder 18)
    - Career Conference, 1996 March (Offsite-box 80, Folder 19)
    - Ellen Coyt Joins Board, 1996 June (Offsite-box 80, Folder 20)
    - End of Summer Celebration, 1996 August (Offsite-box 80, Folder 21)
    - Family Matters Monthly Column, 1996 January (Offsite-box 80, Folder 22)
    - Family Matters Monthly Column, 1996 February (Offsite-box 80, Folder 23)
    - Family Matters Monthly Column, 1996 July (Offsite-box 80, Folder 24)
    - Family Matters Monthly Column, 1996 August (Offsite-box 80, Folder 25)
    - Family Matters Monthly Column, 1996 September (Offsite-box 80, Folder 26)
    - Finest Day Care, Say Happy 190th to Graham Windham, 1996 June (Offsite-box 80, Folder 27)
    - Free and Reduced Meals Program, 1996 September (Offsite-box 80, Folder 28)
    - 190th Birthday Gala honors Brooke Astor and Ruby Bridges Hall, 1996 April (Offsite-box 80, Folder 29)
    - Garden Club Harvest, 1996 October (Offsite-box 80, Folder 30)
    - GW Girls Become Scouts, 1996 January (Offsite-box 80, Folder 31)
    - Halloween Celebrations, 1996 October (Offsite-box 80, Folder 32)
    - Harlem Child Care Center, Ruby Bridges Speaks, 1996 April (Offsite-box 80, Folder 33)
    - Harlem Child Care Graduation, 1996 June (Offsite-box 80, Folder 34)
    - Pam Minetti Joins Board, 1996 June (Offsite-box 80, Folder 35)
    - NAWBO Benefit, 1996 November (Offsite-box 80, Folder 36)
    - Project Welcome Home Barbecue for Formerly Homeless Mothers, 1996 July (Offsite-box 80, Folder 37)
    - Project Welcome Home Graduation, 1996 April (Offsite-box 80, Folder 38)
    - Project Welcome Home Halloween, 1996 October (Offsite-box 80, Folder 39)
    - Tennis Benefit, 1996 July (Offsite-box 80, Folder 40)
    - Tennis Benefit, 1996 August (Offsite-box 80, Folder 41)
    - Gail Donovan Elected to Board, 1996 June (Offsite-box 80, Folder 42)
    - GW Celebrates "Finest" Kids, 1996 June (Offsite-box 80, Folder 43)
    - May Taylor Day - 190th Anniversary, 1996 August (Offsite-box 80, Folder 44)
    - Tennis Clinic, 1996 June (Offsite-box 80, Folder 45)
    - Bronxville HS Seniors join with Graham School Seniors to Beautify Campus, 1996 June (Offsite-box 80, Folder 46)
    - Grads Say Goodbye to Grow With Us, 1996 July (Offsite-box 80, Folder 47)
    - May Taylor Day Press Release, 1997 (Offsite-box 80, Folder 48)
    - Press Releases, 1982-1985 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 1)
    - Press Releases, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 2)
    - The Westchester Historian, Volume 62, Number 4, "Graham Windham: the Story of the Nation's Oldest Childcare Agency", 1986 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 3)
    - Press Releases, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 4)
    - Press Releases, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 5)
    - Articles re: GW, 1987-1990 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 6)
    - Articles re: GW, 1987-1991 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 7)
    - Gala - Arthur Ashe, 1987 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 8)
    - PR re: Ministers' Breakfast, 1988 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 9)
    - Finest Care Clips, 1989 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 10)
    - Press Release re: Wynton Marsalis - Honored at Gala, 1989 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 11)
    - Isabella Graham Award to Wynton Marsalis, 1989 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 12)
    - Articles and Press Releases, 1994-1995 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 13)
    - NY Times Ad, 2006 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 14)
    - Gala, 2007 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 15)
    - New York Nonprofit Press Volume 7 Issue 1, Article re: GW, 2008 January (Offsite-box 81, Folder 16)
    - New York Family profile of Poul Jensen, 2010 December (Offsite-box 81, Folder 17)
    - Press Clips, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 82, Folder 1)
    - Press Clips, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 82, Folder 2)
    - Press Clips, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 82, Folder 3)
    - Press Clips, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 82, Folder 4)
    - Press Clips, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 82, Folder 5)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1980's (Offsite-box 82, Folder 6)
    - Benefit Clips/Celebrities, 1980's (Offsite-box 82, Folder 7)
    - Christmas Card Contest, 1988 (Offsite-box 82, Folder 8)
    - Volunteer Clips, 1988-1991 (Offsite-box 82, Folder 9)
    - Campus Poetry Class, 1986 (Offsite-box 82, Folder 10)
    - International Day, 1986 (Offsite-box 82, Folder 11)
    - Campus All Star Steel Band, 1986 (Offsite-box 82, Folder 12)
    - Hudson River Museum Exhibit, 1987 (Offsite-box 82, Folder 13)
    - NYT, NY Friends, 1987 (Offsite-box 82, Folder 14)
    - Kids Meet Muppets, 1987 (Offsite-box 82, Folder 15)
    - NYT Benefit Listing, 1987 (Offsite-box 82, Folder 16)
    - Harlem Clergy, 1988 (Offsite-box 82, Folder 17)
    - News Clippings re: Child Welfare and City TV Ads, 1990 (Offsite-box 82, Folder 18)
    - Charlotte Ottley elected to Board, 1990 (Offsite-box 82, Folder 19)
    - FPWA Report on Child Welfare Crisis, 1990 (Offsite-box 82, Folder 20)
    - Misc. Articles incl. Manhattan Center, 1990-1993 (Offsite-box 82, Folder 21)
    - Articles re: GW incl. Board Member Phyllis Fisher-Wright, 2002-2005 (Offsite-box 82, Folder 22)
    - Group Homes Christmas Event, undated (Offsite-box 83, Folder 1)
    - Rwanda Relief Month, 1994 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 2)
    - Finest Care Day Care Center Halloween Party, 1994 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 3)
    - Jane Hanson appointed to GW Board, 1994 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 4)
    - Article re: Foster Kids, 1994 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 5)
    - Grow With Us Program, 1994 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 6)
    - Opening of Child Care Center in Harlem, 1994 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 7)
    - Harlem Child Care Center Fundraiser, 1994 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 8)
    - Article re: Homework Program, 1994 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 9)
    - NY City Budget and Children, 1994 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 10)
    - Graham Kids Raise Money for Rwanda, 1994 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 11)
    - May Taylor Day at Campus, 1994-1996 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 12)
    - Profile of GW, 1995 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 13)
    - Articles re: Violence in the Schools, 1994 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 14)
    - CWLA Article re: GW, 1995 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 15)
    - Christmas Article re: GW, 1995 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 16)
    - Brooklyn Preventive Services - Coalition Aids, 1995 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 17)
    - Family Matters re: PTSD, 1995 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 18)
    - Gala - Charlayne Hunter Gault Feted, 1995 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 19)
    - Investiture Ceremony at Campus - Girl Scouts, 1995 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 20)
    - Graham School Graduation, 1995 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 21)
    - First Graduation at Harlem Child Care Center, 1995 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 22)
    - LaToya Edwards, Campus, Carries Olympic Torch, 1995 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 23)
    - Adoption, 1995 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 24)
    - Children and Reading, 1995 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 25)
    - Child Welfare Article and Newt Gingrich, 1995 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 26)
    - Special Needs Children, 1995 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 27)
    - Teaching Children the Value of Money, 1996 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 28)
    - Tennis Program at Campus, 1995-1996 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 29)
    - Article "Orphanages of the '90s" including GW, 1995 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 30)
    - "100 Years of Sanctuary" re: GW, 1995 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 31)
    - Caring Magazine Photo Contest, 1996 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 32)
    - GW's 190th Anniversary Birthday Party at Finest Care, 1996 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 33)
    - Claudia M. Facen Joins Board, 1996 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 34)
    - GW "Culture Camp" Beacon Center, 1996 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 35)
    - Campus Seniors Community Service Project/Spring Cleaning, 1996 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 36)
    - Family Matters Programs, 1996 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 37)
    - Family Matter Conflict Resolution Program, 1996 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 38)
    - GW Benefit, 1996 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 39)
    - Gala, 1996 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 40)
    - Harlem Child Care Center, 1996 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 41)
    - Harlem Child Care Center/Ruby Bridges Hall, 1996 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 42)
    - Margaret Magowan raised 130 Foster Kids, 1996 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 43)
    - Harlem Child Care Center, 1997 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 44)
    - Poul Jensen appointed President, 1997 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 45)
    - Project Welcome Home/Harlem, 1997 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 46)
    - Visibility Campaign, 1997 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 47)
    - Springsteen Concert Event/Auction, 1998 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 48)
    - Nicole Miller Private Sale Benefit, 2000 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 49)
    - Clippings, 1989-1992 (Offsite-box 84, Folder 1)
    - Social Work and Childcare, 1990 (Offsite-box 84, Folder 2)
    - African American Leaders, 1991 (Offsite-box 84, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, 1994 (Offsite-box 84, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous, 1994 (Offsite-box 84, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Clips, 1994 (Offsite-box 84, Folder 6)
    - Family Life, 1994 (Offsite-box 84, Folder 7)
    - Articles re: Children's Social Policy and Budgets, 1994 (Offsite-box 84, Folder 8)
    - Articles re: Children's Social Policy and Budgets, 1994 (Offsite-box 84, Folder 9)
    - Crime and Kids, 1994 (Offsite-box 85, Folder 1)
    - Emergency Foster Boarding Homes/NYC, 1994 (Offsite-box 85, Folder 2)
    - Kwanzaa, 1994 (Offsite-box 85, Folder 3)
    - Orphanages, Group Homes, and Foster Care, 1994 (Offsite-box 85, Folder 4)
    - Re: Schools and Education, 1994 (Offsite-box 85, Folder 5)
    - Re: Adoption, 1994-1995 (Offsite-box 85, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Articles on Welfare and Workfare, Clinton Administration, 1994-1995 (Offsite-box 85, Folder 7)
    - Poverty, Children, and Government, 1994-1995 (Offsite-box 86, Folder 1)
    - Poverty, Children, and Government, 1994-1995 (Offsite-box 86, Folder 2)
    - Misc. Articles on Programs for Children, Govt, etc. incl. Homelessness, 1994-1995 (Offsite-box 86, Folder 3)
    - Articles re: Children's Social Policy and Budgets, 1995 (Offsite-box 86, Folder 4)
    - Articles re: Children's Social Policy and Budgets, 1995 (Offsite-box 86, Folder 5)
    - COFCCA Rally re: Budget Cuts, 1995 (Offsite-box 86, Folder 6)
    - Divorce and Custody, 1995 (Offsite-box 86, Folder 7)
    - NY Times clippings with Graham Windham ads, 2008-2009 (Offsite-box 86, Folder 8)
    - Clippings, 1975-1981 (Offsite-box 144, Volume 216)
    - Clippings, 1981-1986 (Offsite-box 144, Volume 217)
    - Clippings, 1981-1988 (Offsite-box 144, Volume 218)
    - Articles re: NYS and Federal Programs, circa 1989-1994 (Offsite-box OS 3)
    - Articles re: NYS and Federal Programs, circa 1994-1995 (Offsite-box OS 3)
  - Subseries III.9 - Office of Development - Photographic Materials, circa 1978-2010
    The subseries contains seventeen boxes of loose photographs, slides, negatives, contact sheets, and a mock-up of a brochure with photographs attached. It also contains 12 photograph albums.
    Photographic prints are in a variety of formats, including professional photographs commissioned by Graham Windham, and snapshots taken by staff members. Some of the professional photographs in the 1990s were taken by Barbara Hansen. The bulk of the prints in the subseries depict events and activities at various Graham Windham sites. Loose photographic materials were arranged at Graham Windham very roughly by subject (sometimes alphabetically, sometimes not) and/or date. Many photographs from the 1980s are in boxes 87-93, although there are also photographs from that period in subsequent boxes. Most photographs from the 1990s are in boxes 91-103, and most photographs from the 2000s are in boxes 98 and 100. There are very few photographs from the 1970's. Photograph albums are arranged at the end of the subseries.
    - Campus Buildings - prints, 1978 and undated (Offsite-box 87, Folder 1)
    - Campus (?) Unidentified People - prints, circa 1978-1985 (Offsite-box 87, Folder 2)
    - Campus Activities - swimming, basketball, racing - prints, circa 1980 (Offsite-box 87, Folder 3)
    - Campus International Day - prints, slides, negatives, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 87, Folder 4)
    - Hastings Student Project and Luncheon - prints, slides, negatives, 1984 (Offsite-box 87, Folder 5)
    - Campus International Day - prints, slides, negatives, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 87, Folder 6)
    - Greenburgh-Graham Graduation - prints, negatives, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 87, Folder 7)
    - Campus Christmas "Christmas Past" - prints, negatives, 1984-1987 (Offsite-box 87, Folder 8)
    - Christmas In-Kind Gifts - contact sheets, prints, 1988 and undated (Offsite-box 87, Folder 9)
    - Steel Band and Activities - prints, negatives, 1984-2005 and undated (Offsite-box 87, Folder 10)
    - Campus? - prints, circa 1985-1990 (Offsite-box 87, Folder 11)
    - Campus Kids - Adoption Project - prints, negatives, undated (Offsite-box 87, Folder 12)
    - Campus Pool - print, undated (Offsite-box 87, Folder 13)
    - Foster/Daycare Parents Recognition Dinners - prints, negatives, 1983, 1984, circa 1988 (Offsite-box 88, Folder 1)
    - Manhattan Healath Center - prints, contact sheets, negatives, 1984 and undated (Offsite-box 88, Folder 2)
    - Neighborhood Family Services Health Fair - prints, negatives, 1985 (Offsite-box 88, Folder 3)
    - Sweatshirt Painting Party - prints, 1989 (Offsite-box 88, Folder 4)
    - Gala - Joan Ganz Cooney - prints, slides, negatives, contact Sheets, correspondence, 1988 (Offsite-box 88, Folder 5)
    - Independence Day Fair - contact sheets 1987 [with unrelated prints 1983 and undated], circa 1983-1987 (Offsite-box 88, Folder 6)
    - May Taylor Day - prints, negatives, 1986 (Offsite-box 88, Folder 7)
    - Day Care Center - prints, undated (Offsite-box 88, Folder 8)
    - Family Day Care - contact sheets, negatives, undated (Offsite-box 88, Folder 9)
    - Family Services - prints, negatives, undated (Offsite-box 88, Folder 10)
    - Foster Care Families - prints, negatives, circa 1981-1988 (Offsite-box 88, Folder 11)
    - Foster Care and Adoption - prints, slides, negatives, 1981, 1983, 1988 and undated (Offsite-box 88, Folder 12)
    - Events at Campus including May Taylor Day - prints, negatives, circa 1980-1985 (Offsite-box 88, Folder 13)
    - Staff and Board - prints, negatives, slides, contact sheets, 1980-1984 and undated (Offsite-box 89, Folder 1)
    - Hudson River Museum Exhibit Photos - prints, negatives, contact sheets, 1987 and undated (Offsite-box 89, Folder 2)
    - A Makeup Workshop on Campus - prints, negatives, 1984 (Offsite-box 89, Folder 3)